{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": "What God did on the seventh day? (Genesis 2:2-3) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Create children for the man and woman "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Rest"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Create wind "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Light "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Rest",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "The sequence of the day and night began on what day (Gen. 1:5)? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "First"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Second"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Third "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Fourth"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "First",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God made the man out of ________?  (Genesis 2:7) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Stone"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Dew"
        },
        {
          "choice": "A piece of His own body "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Dust"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Dust",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did God place His human creations? (Genesis 2:15-22)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Garden"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Paradise"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Zion "
        },
        {
          "choice": "The wilderness"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Garden",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God create the woman out of _________?  (Genesis 2:18)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Dust "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Dew"
        },
        {
          "choice": "From the rib of man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Stone   "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "From the rib of man",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did God create  woman ________?  (Genesis 2:22-24)",
      "time": "20000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "So she could oversee the man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "So she could keep the man company"
        },
        {
          "choice": "So she could serve the man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "So she could help the man"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "So she could help the man",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who named the living creatures? (Genesis 2:20)",
      "time": "20000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "God"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Adam & Eve"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Eve"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Adam"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Adam",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God command the following to Adam and Eve except? (Genesis 1:28) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Have dominion over all living things "
        },
        {
          "choice": "Work and be industrious"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Be fruitful and multiply"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Subdue the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Work and be industrious",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did God create humans? (Genesis 1:26-27) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "In His image"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Through evolution of primates"
        },
        {
          "choice": "The goodness and love"
        },
        {
          "choice": "The dust of the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "In His image",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God call the dry land and the waters? (Genesis 1:20) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "Mountains; Oceans"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Valleys; Lakes"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Earth; Seas"
        },
        {
          "choice": "Stone; Water "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "Earth; Seas",
      "type": "epi_2"
    }
  ]
}